<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hybrid prediction notes</title>
    <link>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hybrid prediction notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hydrology meeting notes</title>
      <link>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/05/05/hydrology-meeting-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/05/05/hydrology-meeting-notes/</guid>
      <description>Present  …   Since last time  bugfix submitted to Zongyi Li code updated to pytorch 1.8 (faster) Additional bug: the code is BAD for impossible flows challenge: out-of-distribution predictions are terrible   Discussions  Next steps  References Farkas, Kata, Luke S. Hillary, Shelagh K. Malham, James E. McDonald, and David L. Jones. 2020. “Wastewater and Public Health: The Potential of Wastewater Surveillance for Monitoring COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydrology meeting notes</title>
      <link>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/04/21/hydrology-meeting-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/04/21/hydrology-meeting-notes/</guid>
      <description>Present  Tao Cui Petra Kuhnert Dan Pagendam David Robertson Dan MacKinlay   Since last time Simulation progress Tao and Dan have been working on generic simulations via MODFLOW to match the neural emulator. Plan to get modflow output that includes
time-step data, not simply the data from the end of each stress period parse HDS-output to access this from python. Tao has provided scripts for this  Notes on Li et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydrology meeting notes</title>
      <link>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/03/24/hydrology-meeting-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/03/24/hydrology-meeting-notes/</guid>
      <description>Present  Dan Pagendam Tao Cui Dan MacKinlay   Since last time Dan M implemented the Li et al. (2020) method, trained it (Navier Stokes version) and tested it on artificial data.
 Discussions  Dan M Questions
 can we get gradient out of MODFLOW sims?
Tao: from alternative version Dan M: I think this is low priority now
 how close to advection-diffusion are we in groundwater?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydrology meeting notes</title>
      <link>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/03/10/hydrology-meeting-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/03/10/hydrology-meeting-notes/</guid>
      <description>Present  Dan MacKinlay Petra Kuhnert Dan Pagendam   Since last time Dan M has been reviewing alternative techniques from the literature for non-stationary PDEs
 Weak formulation Bao et al. (2020); Zang et al. (2020). This is very clever, but does not solve the problem that it is hard to use the “implicit representation” output, and it is hard to see how it could generalise to multiple problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydrology meeting notes</title>
      <link>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/02/24/hydrology-meeting-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/2021/02/24/hydrology-meeting-notes/</guid>
      <description>Present  Dan Pagendam Tao Cui Dan MacKinlay   Since last time  Dan M ran a reading group on Physics informed NNs under undertainty (Raissi, Perdikaris, and Karniadakis 2019; Zhang et al. 2019) Consolidated all notes into a repository https://github.com/csiro-mlai/HybridPredictionReview/ Published online at csiro-mlai.github.io/HybridPredictionReview/   Discussions Tao on Ensembling and subspace methods (Siade, Putti, and Yeh 2010; Tonkin and Doherty 2009; White 2018)
 Next steps  Dan M: Non-stationary inference methods investigation, e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
